<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhoneticsMaster</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-9485903417823396~4969515254</string>
    <string name="ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-9485903417823396/9747199210</string>
    <string name="test_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>

    <string name="introductionText">
        Phonetics\n
        It is the branch of acoustics concerned with speech processes including its production and perception and acoustic analysis.
        Basically, it is the study of speech sounds.\n\n
        The Phonetics Chart\n
        There are twenty-six (26) alphabets in English Language–five (5) vowels and twenty-one (21) consonants. However, these alphabets are pronounced inconsistently because there are more sounds in the language than the alphabets. There are forty-four (44) sounds in English: twenty (20) vowel sounds–eight pure vowel sounds or monophthong and twelve diphthongs–and twenty-four (24) consonant sounds.
        At a first glance at the phonetics chart, it looks like a meaningless collection of symbols, however, these symbols represent distinct sounds.
    </string>
    <string name="mono_top_row">Front Vowels (tongue towards front)</string>
    <string name="mono_middle_row">Centre Vowels (tongue relatively flat)</string>
    <string name="mono_bot_row">Back Vowels (tongue pulled back)</string>
    <string name="consonant_expl">A consonant sound is made by blocking the air as it leaves the mouth.
            We use the tongue, lips, teeth, mouth and throat to block air.
            Some sounds use the voice (voiced), others only air (voiceless).\n\n
            The second and the last columns are voiceless and the others are voiced.
    </string>
    <string name="diphthongs_expl">They are vowel sounds that start near the articulatory position for one vowel and move toward the position for another</string>
    <string name="monopthong_expl">A vowel sound (diphthong and monophthong) is made by shaping air as it leaves the mouth.
We use the articulators to shape the air - lips, jaw, tongue.</string>

</resources>
